



# **Luong Quoc Khang**

- **10/12/1997**
- **\**0792155597
- P Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

- Male
- ☑ QuocKhangLuong1012@gmail.com
- i https://www.facebook.com/quockhang.luo ng

## SUMMARY

I'm a fourth years student at university of information technology with a good knowledge in C#.NET technologies, knowledge of Object - Oriented programming, Analysis and design, Database and some Design patterns.

I'm a team-player because I like to help other and learn from them what I don't know. I worked at different positions in team such as programmer, designer, analyst or sometime I was a trainer to help team members to approach new technology which will be used in project.

I want to take advantages of programming skills & experience and understanding of technology to become a better developer.

## **EDUCATION**

MAJOR: SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

7/2015 - Now

#### UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

GPA: 7.9/10

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### INTERN AT KYANON DIGITAL

6/2018 - 8/2018

#### **KYANON DIGITAL**

Main responsibilities:

- Add new features to company project
- Fix bugs, error
- write document
- learn new technology

#### Recognition and Gains:

- Learnt AngulaJS, ASP.NET MVC, migration database,...

#### FUJINET SYSTEM JSC - TRAIL STAFF FUJINET SYSTEM JSC

18/11/2018 - 26/1/2019

- Read and review, modified designed file of customer
- program some features that depends on customer design using knockoutJS, asp.net
- Write unit test and test document
- test and review

Achievements and skills gained:

- learnt new technology like

## **SKILLS**

C# / .NET

SQL

Javascript

**ASP.NET MVC** 

Javascript

Logical thinking and creative

**Public Speaking** 

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Framework:

o Database: Entity Framework

o Ninject

o EPPlus , ...

- Database :

o MS SQL server

o Azure SQL database

**Version Control:** 

o Git, SVN .MS project

- Soft Skills:

o Time management

o Self-taught

o Teamwork

- Others:

o Good understanding of OOP

o SOLID principle, dependency injection

o Testing: selenium, unit test

o Design pattern: singleton, Adapter,

dependency insersion

o AngularJS, Ajax, JQuery, KnockoutJS,

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

TOEIC Certificate with score 775 2017